kentlaw.edu 2019-12-11

# Privacy Statement | Chicago-Kent College of Law

## _Chicago-Kent College of Law at Illinois Institute of Technology (Chicago-Kent)_

This is a privacy statement for the website and pages of Chicago-Kent College of Law, an academic unit of Illinois Institute of Technology. Chicago-Kent is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit its web pages. This statement is intended to inform you concerning what information Chicago-Kent collects while you browse our web pages, how we utilize this information and your options with respect to the same. The information disclosed in this statement is subject to change periodically in the sole discretion of Chicago-Kent. Your continued use of our site implies your understanding and acceptance of this privacy statement.

### Personally Identifying Information

As used in this statement, personally identifying information refers to any information that can be used to identify, contact or locate an individual, and may include such items as name, mailing or email addresses, or telephone number. Chicago-Kent does not collect your personally identifying information when you visit our website unless you choose to provide such information to us; providing such information is strictly voluntary. Chicago-Kent does not sell or rent to third parties personally identifying information submitted by visitors to our website, and we will not share such information with third parties except as required by law. We may share quantitative, non-personal data about our site visitors with affiliates, sponsors, institutional partners and other third parties.

### Cookies

Like most websites, we use a feature of your browser to set a "cookie" on your computer. Cookies are small text files that reside on your computer and that identify you, anonymously, as a unique visitor. Our use of cookies does not reveal to us your personal information based solely on our use of the cookie. We use cookies to analyze traffic patterns and user interests, track user movement within our website, and gather broad demographic information (e.g., age and gender) for aggregate use for reporting purposes. Reputable web browsers will enable you to reject cookies or to choose which cookies you will accept. Please be advised that disabling cookies through your web browser may interfere with or prohibit your ability to enjoy the full functionality of our site.

[Learn more about cookies and how you can disable them in your browser.](https://cookiesandyou.com/)

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to monitor and collect certain information about the use of this site, and to adjust our content to better serve the needs of the viewer. Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is subject to [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.

### Third-Party Ad Networks, Remarketing and Behavioral Advertising

Although this website does not present advertising from third parties, we may participate in behaviorial advertising of our own programs on other websites via digital advertising networks from Google, Facebook, LinkedIn and comparable services to create custom audiences for remarketing as well as to target similar audiences based on interests. This means that we may use cookies, pixel tags or analogous technologies from such networks to help measure ad performance (conversion tracking) and to identify you as having visited our website and other sites on the internet so that the networks can provide advertising about products and services tailored to your interests. If you would like to opt-out of third-party behavioral advertising that collects information on your use of this and other websites, you can do so by visiting the [_Network Advertising Initiative_](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and the [_Digital Advertising Alliance_](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

### Use of Links

Throughout our web pages we provide links to third-party websites which may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for, and exercise no control over, these organizations, their views, or the accuracy of the information contained on these other websites.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us at [webmaster@kentlaw.iit.edu](mailto:webmaster@kentlaw.iit.edu).

_Effective February 2017_
